This should be far enough
away from civilization,
considering I don't know
what's about to happen.
A job-change quest...
That's the quest that showed up after
I passed level 40 from the last raid.
I've run into two dungeons
accessible with key items before,
but the only quests I've been forced
to take on immediately
were the penalty and emergency ones.
This one, however, seems to be optional,
and I've been given time to decide.
Should I assume that means it's going
to be that much more difficult?
The logical assumption is that this is an
important event that'll make me stronger
by earning skills best suited to my job...
Yes.
Oh, shoot, my daily quest...
I guess I can do it when I get back.
All right. Looks like
the real game starts here.
I wonder what's waiting for me inside?
Should be interesting.
I apologize for the delay.
No, you're right on time, Jinsung.
It's been a while, Jinho.
Brother...
The dungeon seems surprisingly normal so far.
I can't use potions or full recovery?
Or leave until the quest is finished.
I'm gonna need to be pretty careful, then.
An armor-type beast?
That didn't work?
No good.
I've fought enemies...
with hard exteriors before!
I wasted a use of Fatal Strike...
and when I can't recover mana
or heal damage, too.
But...
It's not like they care, of course.
What is it, Jinho?
You've barely touched your food.
Oh, nothing...
Jinsung, how are things going
with establishing the guild?
I've heard the S-Ranks you've been
making offers to have all declined.
It's true that Hunters Min Byung-gu
and Cha Hae-in turned me down,
but it won't be an issue.
I've got negotiations underway with
European and Middle Eastern hunters.
They're likely to sign
if we agree to their terms.
It'll be similar to the case
of Hunter Hwang Dongsoo.
You've got a point.
Hunters from overseas. Of course...
Jinho.
I know you've been working on
something of your own in secret.
Buying up the rights to all these
C-Rank raids at a high price,
trying to establish your credentials.
And that's fine, for a personal project, but...
Don't even think about getting in my way.
He doesn't know about the boss.
If he had any idea of the kind of power
I have on my side...!
I guess even I get tired
after this much combat.
Better catch my breath—
The Stealth skill?!
I've gotta deal with beasts
that can use that, too?!
On top of that, there's a mage...
and one that uses light magic, at that.
The stealth skill and light magic...
What is going on here?
That armor reminded me of the Kasaka, too.
It's like I'm revisiting my past battles.
This quest is even tougher than I imagined!
The different kinds of beast
all have different weaknesses.
Knights require strength, assassins take
perception, archers need agility...
Without enough strength,
the knights won't take damage.
Without enough perception,
the assassins can't be detected.
And the real issue is the mages.
They probably need intellect as a counter,
but I haven't really invested in that stat.
Which means I don't have much mana.
I need to conserve my skills...
but my fatigue is starting to build up.
I need to end this soon!
I see you're all here.
The time has finally come.
I'm just glad the beasts
drop stuff like this, too.
A High-Rank Knight's Chestplate?
Come to think of it, I haven't really
experimented with gear much.
It can turn invisible?!
I'm glad I don't have to stand out.
Looks like it doesn't restrict
my movement, either.
It's kind of hard to tell without being
fully restored, but my level has gone up.
I've got plenty of gold and items, too.
With my fatigue recovered,
I may as well move onto the next stage.
Now, then...
How bad is it gonna be
on the other side of this door?
But if I can't get out of here without
getting through, I just have to press on.
Something about that gust
just gave me the chills...
Some kind of throne room?
This sight, these sounds, the way it feels...
My entire body remembers.
This is pressure on the level of what
I felt during the double dungeon!
And all of that intensity
is coming from this guy!
"Knight Commander Igris the Bloodred."
Name's red, too...
He really is nothing like
the enemies I've fought so far!
A knight who defends an empty throne...
Here he comes!
He chops through pillars
like they're dry branches!
This is beyond just strong!
To be able to move this quickly,
in that heavy armor...
What a monster!
Still no good!
We're equals in terms of speed.
But he's much more powerful.
And because of that armor,
my dagger isn't doing anything.
Do I have any way of beating this guy?
He's even more dangerous than I thought.
Still...
I doubt I can win without a weapon,
but this is the only way I can think of
to deal any damage through that armor!
I guess you're being chivalrous, huh?
You must think this is gonna be easy.
Come in.
Chairman, you still haven't gone home?
I don't feel like calling it a day just yet.
So I've been dealing with
a bit of work that's piled up.
Likewise.
I've been clearing some
non-urgent items off my plate.
So it's finally happening.
Indeed.
Speak of the devil.
I'm here. Are you heading out soon?
Yes, sir.
I wanted to thank you before that.
I'm grateful you approved this operation.
No thanks necessary.
It's all because you've kept Jeju Island's
name afloat in the interviews
you've been doing on TV and in print.
That's kept it in the public's consciousness
and is swaying their opinion.
All I did was help tip the scales a bit.
You don't expect criticism
for kicking a hornet's nest?
I'm prepared to take the brunt of that.
Just be careful out there.
Jeju Island is dangerous business.
I'm fully aware, sir.
This expedition is about
assessing threat levels.
We'll prod the enemy and see how
and to what degree they respond.
As diligent as ever, I see.
The third raid on Jeju Island...
To me, that battle...
never really ended.
So fast!
Even though I blocked,
it felt like that took down 500 HP!
I made the right move putting armor on.
There's a chance taking it
full on would've killed me.
For him to deal this kind of damage
even without his sword...
He's too damn strong!
If I can't compete in terms of power,
then I'll boost my speed!
I can't catch him!
That passive skill boosted my defense!
That oughta do.
I...
haven't...
lost yet!
That dagger can't change owners like that!
It'll go back into my inventory,
and then back into my hand!
Too shallow!
Have to stab deeper!
I won... right?
That... was a close one.
My winning was pretty much a fluke.
In terms of skills, ability, and experience...
There was a real difference
between us on every level.
One screwup, and I'd probably be dead.
Four rewards, huh?
A pouch with 1,500,000 gold in it.
The same helmet that Igris had...
and it's an S-Rank item!
The key to the Demon's Castle
was S-Rank, too,
but I've never had gear
of that quality before.
It reduces physical damage by 15%,
along with a 20-point boost
to strength and vitality!
That's tasty!
Along with a rune stone
for the Ruler's Hand...
What kind of skill is that?
I guess I'll figure it out later.
But what about...
this "instant teleportation stone"?
It won't go into the inventory.
Why give me a teleportation stone now?
Is... Is the job-change quest...
not over yet?
"Survive as long as possible"?
"Enhancement points"?
And what is a "higher class"?
"Good luck," huh?
Wait, am I facing infinite
waves of enemies?!
If they were as strong as Igris,
I would've been overwhelmed in seconds...
But these guys?
I can handle them easily enough.
Still... There's an awful lot of them!
Damn it! I keep fighting, but the gates
keep puking up more!
I think the key to this quest
is how long you can last.
In that case...
Stealth costs 200 mana to activate,
and then one for each second of use...
I have 190 left.
I'll buy as much time as I can!
They saw through Stealth?!
This is worse than I thought!
I won't be able to use Stealth
or Murderous Intent anymore!
How long has it been?
Only five minutes?!
I can't keep going!
I hate to do it, but I'd better use
that teleportation stone...